{
    "id": "a1cee98e33394db3b5167508362f0ac8",
    "title": "Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He showed me a photo. / I ...................................... a photo by him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had shown",
                "was shown",
                "have shown"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c0a26e3e2b654a17bf3ce8ef63dd5a1a"
        },
        {
            "question": "This box contains chocolates. / Chocolates ............................... in this box.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are containing",
                "are contained",
                "have contained"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "39e9555434ee4ef98e9efe4edd8c34f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who does not hate liars? / By whom ............................. liars not hated?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "have",
                "is"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b4f77528a5244403ac2c6fb684c5dbed"
        },
        {
            "question": "Solve this problem. / Let this problem .............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is solved",
                "be solved",
                "has solved"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4b69df7d74a84feba0c01ab62cfabde2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I expect you to do the work. / You .................................... to do this work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "expected",
                "are expected",
                "have expected"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "59be3d3bf10c4df59a68d1b5a6bc802f"
        },
        {
            "question": "His conduct shocked his mother. / His mother .................................. by his conduct.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shocked",
                "was shocked",
                "had shocked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bb16fd5efd544ff58732a944905b962c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He could do nothing. / Nothing .................................... by him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can be done",
                "could done",
                "could be done"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f2871d9042c14b41b93e52a80ee873ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know this gentleman? / Is this gentleman ............................... to you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "knew",
                "known"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3bdd6a96059e41e8b09a59f40b5a8e80"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do not tease the animals. / Let the animals not ....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "be teasing",
                "teased",
                "be teased"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9f79c2f137b843d190a0b1edb2cd2039"
        },
        {
            "question": "Lower the price. /Let the price ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "be lower",
                "be lowered",
                "is lowered"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "21d48074702e42809d130a4a0e22708a"
        }
    ]
}